Guide to the Religious Education Association Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Meetings, Series IV
  - National R.E.A. Meetings
    - 1979 Convention
      - Leadership (Box 56, Folder 623-624)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 56, Folder 625)
    - 1981 Convention
      - Planning (Box 57, Folder 626-628)
      - Program (Box 57, Folder 629-635)
      - Attendance (Box 58, Folder 636)
      - Finance (Box 58, Folder 637)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 58, Folder 638-640)
    - 1983 Convention
      - Planning (Box 58, Folder 641-647)
      - Planning (Box 59, Folder 648-651)
      - Finance (Box 59, Folder 652-656)
      - Finance (Box 60, Folder 657-661)
      - Leadership (Box 60, Folder 662-665)
      - Leadership (Box 61, Folder 666-669)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 61, Folder 670-676)
      - Promotion/Interpretation (Box 62, Folder 677-679)
      - Program (Box 62, Folder 680)
  - Regional, co-sponsored or special conferences, meetings
    - Conference of C.E. agencies, Long Island, 1921 (Box 63, Folder 681)
    - R.E.A. Chicago and New York area conferences, 1924 (Box 63, Folder 681)
    - R.E.A. Eastern Conference, NYC, 1938 (Box 63, Folder 681)
    - 65th Anniversary of Religious Education - Banquet, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 682-685)
    - "Religious Education in a Pluralistic Society" - Ecumenical Study Commission, Toronto, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 686-687)
    - "Writers Project Conference", Rensselaerville, NY, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 688-689)
    - "Ecumenical Consultation on Education", NYC, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 690)
    - R.E.A. Eastern Regional Conference, Atlantic City, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 691-693)
    - R.E.A. Eastern Regional Conference, Atlantic City, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 694)
    - LEAD Consultants/R.E.A. Conference, Pittsburgh, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 695)
    - "Faith Without Prejudice" Conference, sponsored by The American Jewish Committee, St. Louis, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 696)
    - Project Forward '76 Consultation, Conference, 1975, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 697-701)
    - 70th Anniversary of Religious Education - Banquet, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 702)
    - Adult Education Association / R.E.A. Conference, NYC, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 703)
    - Adult Education Association / R.E.A. Conference, NYC, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 704-709)
    - A.E.A./N.A.P.C.A.E./R.E.A. Conference, Detroit, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 710-712)
    - Conference on "The Study of Ethics and Religions: Does the Public School Have a Role?", New Haven, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 713-714)
    - Conference on "The Study of Ethics and Religions: Does the Public School Have a Role?", New Haven (Box 66, Folder 715-718)
    - 75th Anniversary Seminar - Tour to Israel, Rome, Geneva, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 719-720)
    - 75th Anniversary Celebration, Chicago, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 721-726)
    - 75th Anniversary Celebration, Chicago (Box 67, Folder 727-729)
    - Seminar/Forum on the Sunday School, Nashville, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 730-731)
    - International Seminar on Religious Education and Values, Second meeting, Schenectady, NY, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 732)
    - Conference on Religious Education and Public Policy, NYC, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 733)
- Regional Work, Series V
  Scope and Contents
  This Series is divided into two sections: Administrative Files and Chapter Records. The Administrative Files are arranged chronologically with two sub-sections: correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek dating from 1965-1967 which is alphabetically arranged and membership cultivation files of Cheek during the same time period which are divided according to interest groups. The Chapter Records are arranged alphabetically by state, and by local areas within states. The files for each chapter are arranged chronologically. Records for the New York Metropolitan Area are divided into three sections: Minutes,Financial records, and General.
  - Administrative Files
    - Newsletter to Regional Chairmen (see Program Committee, Series II for early regional activities) (Box 68, Folder 735)
    - Regional visits of Harrison Elliott (See also: Series III) (Box 68, Folder 736)
    - Program suggestions, summary of regional visits (Box 68, Folder 737)
    - Selection of A. Wilson Cheek as Associate General Secretary (Box 68, Folder 739)
    - Resignation of A. Wilson Cheek as Associate General Secretary (Box 68, Folder 740)
    - Reports, lists, policy guidelines (Box 68, Folder 741-742)
    - Correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek:A (Box 68, Folder 743)
    - Correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek: B - C (Box 68, Folder 744)
    - Correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek: D - G (Box 68, Folder 745)
    - Correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek: H (Box 68, Folder 746)
    - Correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek: I - K (Box 68, Folder 747)
    - Correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek: L (Box 68, Folder 748)
    - Correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek: M (Box 68, Folder 749)
    - Correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek: Mundlein College (Box 68, Folder 750)
    - Correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek: N - P (Box 68, Folder 751)
    - Correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek: Q - S (Box 68, Folder 752)
    - Correspondence of A. Wilson Cheek: T - Z (Box 68, Folder 753)
    - Membership cultivation work of A. Wilson Cheek: General (Box 69, Folder 754)
    - Membership cultivation work of A. Wilson Cheek: Letters to special interest groups (Box 69, Folder 755-757)
    - Membership cultivation work of A. Wilson Cheek: Catholic laymen luncheons (Box 69, Folder 758)
    - Membership cultivation work of A. Wilson Cheek: Jewish laymen luncheon (Box 69, Folder 759)
    - Membership cultivation work of A. Wilson Cheek: Protestant laymen and women (Box 69, Folder 760)
    - Membership cultivation work of A. Wilson Cheek: Montclair Consultation on Religious Education in Public Schools (Box 69, Folder 761)
    - Inquiries re. R.E.A. chapters (post-Cheek era) (Box 69, Folder 762)
    - Regional work during Kathan era (Box 69, Folder 763)
  - Chapter records
    - Arizona (Box 69, Folder 764)
    - California: San Francisco Bay area (Box 69, Folder 765)
    - California: San Francisco Bay area, 1953-1954 Jul (Box 69, Folder 766)
    - California: San Francisco Bay area, 1954 Aug-Nov (Box 69, Folder 767)
    - California: San Francisco Bay area, 1955-1956 (Box 69, Folder 768)
    - California: San Francisco Bay area, 1959-1960 (Box 69, Folder 769)
    - California: San Francisco Bay area, 1966-1967 May (Box 70, Folder 770)
    - California: San Francisco Bay area, 1970 Jun-1976 (Box 70, Folder 771)
    - California: Southern California (Box 70, Folder 772)
    - California: Southern California, 1951 (Box 70, Folder 773)
    - California: Southern California (Box 70, Folder 774)
    - California: Southern California, 1954 Jun - Nov (Box 70, Folder 775)
    - California: Southern California, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 776)
    - California: Southern California, 1956 Jan-Apr (Box 70, Folder 777)
    - California: Southern California, 1956 May-Dec (Box 70, Folder 778)
    - California: Southern California, 1957-1958 (Box 70, Folder 779)
    - California: Southern California, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 780)
    - California: Southern California, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 781)
    - California: Southern California, 1961-1963 (Box 70, Folder 782)
    - California: Stockton (Box 70, Folder 783)
    - California:, 1956-1957 (Box 70, Folder 784)
    - Colorado (Box 70, Folder 785)
    - Connecticut: Bridgeport (Box 70, Folder 786)
    - Connecticut: Hartford (Box 70, Folder 787)
    - Connecticut: Hartford, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 788)
    - Connecticut: Hartford, 1954-1955 (Box 71, Folder 789)
    - Connecticut: Hartford, 1956-1957 (Box 71, Folder 790)
    - Connecticut: Hartford, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 791)
    - Connecticut: Hartford, 1966 Jan-Mar (Box 71, Folder 792)
    - Connecticut: Hartford, 1966 Apr-Jul (Box 71, Folder 793)
    - Connecticut: Hartford (Box 71, Folder 794)
    - Connecticut: Hartford, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 795)
    - Connecticut: Hartford, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 796)
    - Connecticut: Hartford, 1970-1973 (Box 71, Folder 797)
    - Connecticut: New Haven (Box 71, Folder 798)
    - Connecticut: New Haven, 1966 Apr-Sep (Box 71, Folder 799)
    - Connecticut: New Haven, 1966 Nov-1967 (Box 71, Folder 800)
    - Connecticut: New Haven, 1968-1969 (Box 71, Folder 801)
    - Connecticut: New Haven, 1970-1973 (Box 71, Folder 802)
    - Connecticut chapter (merger of Hartford and New Haven chapters), 1974-1975 (Box 71, Folder 803)
    - Connecticut chapter (merger of Hartford and New Haven chapters), 1976-1979 (Box 71, Folder 804)
    - District of Columbia (Box 72, Folder 805)
    - District of Columbia, 1953-1954 (Box 72, Folder 806)
    - District of Columbia, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 807)
    - District of Columbia, 1967, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 808)
    - Florida, 1941, 1956-1957, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 809)
    - Georgia: Atlanta, 1952-1954 (Box 72, Folder 810)
    - Georgia: Atlanta, 1955-1956 (Box 72, Folder 811)
    - Georgia: Atlanta, 1966-1967 (Box 72, Folder 812)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1942, 1950-1951 (Box 72, Folder 813)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1952-1953 (Box 72, Folder 814)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 815)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 816)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 817)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 818)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1960 (Box 72, Folder 819)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 820)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 821)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 822)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1964 Jan-Jul (Box 73, Folder 823)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1964 Aug-Dec (Box 73, Folder 824)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1965 Jan-Jul (Box 73, Folder 825)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1965 Aug-Dec (Box 73, Folder 826)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 827)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 828)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 829)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 830)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 831)
    - Illinois: Chicago, 1971-1976 (Box 73, Folder 832)
    - Illinois: Evanston, 1950-1952 (Box 73, Folder 833)
    - Illinois: Evanston, 1953-1956 (Box 74, Folder 834)
    - Indiana: Fort Wayne, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 835)
    - Indiana: Indianapolis (Box 74, Folder 835)
    - Iowa: Ames, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 836)
    - Iowa: Davenport, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 837)
    - Iowa: Des Moines, 1951-1956 (Box 74, Folder 838)
    - Iowa: Dubuque, 1965-1973 (Box 74, Folder 839)
    - Iowa: Iowa City, 1953-1954 (Box 74, Folder 840)
    - Kansas, 1956-1960 (Box 74, Folder 841)
    - Kentucky: Lexington, 1951-1954 (Box 74, Folder 842)
    - Kentucky: Louisville, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 843)
    - Kentucky: Louisville, 1954-1955 (Box 74, Folder 844)
    - Kentucky: Louisville, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 845)
    - Louisiana, 1954-1958 (Box 74, Folder 846)
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1965-1966 (Box 74, Folder 847)
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 848)
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1968-1970 (Box 74, Folder 849)
    - Maryland: Baltimore, 1971-1974 (Box 74, Folder 850)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1934, 1951-1952 (Box 74, Folder 851)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 852)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1954-1955 (Box 74, Folder 853)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1956 (Box 74, Folder 854)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1957-1959 (Box 74, Folder 855)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1960-1961 (Box 74, Folder 856)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 857)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1963-1964 (Box 74, Folder 858)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1965 Mar-Apr (Box 75, Folder 859)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1965 Oct-Dec (Box 75, Folder 860)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1966 Jan-Feb (Box 75, Folder 861)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1966 Mar-Apr (Box 75, Folder 862)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1966 Jun-Dec (Box 75, Folder 863)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 864)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1968 Jan-Oct (Box 75, Folder 865)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1968 Nov-Dec (Box 75, Folder 866)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1968 Jan-Feb (Box 75, Folder 867)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1969 Mar-Dec (Box 75, Folder 868)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 869)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1971-1972 (Box 75, Folder 870)
    - Massachusetts: Boston, 1973-1974 (Box 75, Folder 871)
    - Michigan: Detroit (Box 75, Folder 872)
    - Michigan: Detroit, 1956-1959 (Box 75, Folder 873)
    - Michigan: Detroit, 1966 Aug (Box 75, Folder 874)
    - Michigan: Detroit, 1966 Sep-Oct (Box 75, Folder 875)
    - Michigan: Detroit, 1966 Nov-Dec (Box 76, Folder 876)
    - Michigan: Detroit, 1967-1970 (Box 76, Folder 877)
    - Minnesota: Minneapolis, 1954, 1966-1967 (Box 76, Folder 878)
    - Missouri: Kansas City, 1950 (Box 76, Folder 879)
    - Missouri: St. Louis, 1953-1961 (Box 76, Folder 880)
    - New Hampshire, 1954 (Box 76, Folder 881)
    - New Jersey, 1953, 1965, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 882)
    - New Jersey, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 883)
    - New Jersey, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 884)
    - New York: Albany, Schenectady, Utica, Syracuse, 1953-1967 (Box 76, Folder 885)
    - New York: Buffalo, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 886)
    - New York: Buffalo, 1954-1956 (Box 76, Folder 887)
    - New York: Buffalo, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 888)
    - New York: Buffalo, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 889)
    - New York: Buffalo, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 890)
    - New York: Buffalo, 1968-1975, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 891)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: Minutes, 1940-1965 (Box 76, Folder 892)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: Minutes, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 893)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: Minutes, 1967-1972, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 894)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: Financial Records, 1965 (Box 77, Folder 895)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1940-1951 (Box 77, Folder 896)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1952 Jan-Aug (Box 77, Folder 897)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1952 Oct (Box 77, Folder 898)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1952 Nov (Box 77, Folder 899)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1952 Dec (Box 77, Folder 900)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1953 Jan-Mar (Box 77, Folder 901)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1953 Apr (Box 77, Folder 902)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1953 May-Jul (Box 77, Folder 903)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1953 Sep-Dec (Box 77, Folder 904)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 905)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 906)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1956 Jan-Oct (Box 77, Folder 907)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1956 Nov-Dec (Box 77, Folder 908)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1958-1960 (Box 78, Folder 909)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1965 Jan-Sep (Box 78, Folder 910)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1965 Oct (Box 78, Folder 911)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1965 Nov (Box 78, Folder 912)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1965 Dec (Box 78, Folder 913)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1966 Jan (Box 78, Folder 914)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1966 Feb (Box 78, Folder 915)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1966 Mar (Box 78, Folder 916)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1966 Apr (Box 78, Folder 917)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1966 May (Box 78, Folder 918)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1966 Jun-Aug (Box 78, Folder 919)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1966 Sep-Oct (Box 78, Folder 920)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1966 Nov-Dec (Box 79, Folder 921)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1967 Jan-Mar (Box 79, Folder 922)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1967 Apr-Jun (Box 79, Folder 923)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1967 Jul-Oct (Box 79, Folder 924)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1967 Nov-Dec (Box 79, Folder 925)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1968 Jan-Apr (Box 79, Folder 926)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1968 May-Dec (Box 79, Folder 927)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1969 Jan-Mar (Box 79, Folder 928)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1969 Apr-Dec (Box 79, Folder 929)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1970 Jan-Mar (Box 79, Folder 930)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1970 Apr-Aug (Box 79, Folder 931)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1970 Sep-Dec (Box 79, Folder 932)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1971 Jan-Jun (Box 79, Folder 933)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1971 Jul-Oct (Box 79, Folder 934)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1971 Nov-Dec (Box 79, Folder 935)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 936)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1973-1975 (Box 80, Folder 937)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, 1976-1979 (Box 80, Folder 938)
    - New York Metropolitan Area: General, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 939-940)
    - New York: Rochester, 1953, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 941)
    - New York: Rochester, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 942)
    - New York: Rochester, 1968, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 943)
    - New York: Syracuse, 1956, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 944)
    - New York: Syracuse, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 945)
    - North Carolina, 1954-1956 (Box 80, Folder 946)
    - Ohio: Cincinnati, 1953, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 947)
    - Ohio: Cincinnati, 1966-1968 (Box 80, Folder 948)
    - Ohio: Cleveland, 1942, 1952, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 949)
    - Ohio: Cleveland, 1966-1968 (Box 80, Folder 950)
    - Ohio: Columbus, 1953-1959 (Box 80, Folder 951)
    - Ohio: Dayton, 1954-1956 (Box 80, Folder 952)
    - Ohio: Toledo, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 953)
    - Oregon, 1954-1969 (Box 80, Folder 954)
    - Pennsylvania: Lancaster, 1954, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 955)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1950-1952 (Box 81, Folder 956)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1953-1954 (Box 81, Folder 957)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1964-1965 (Box 81, Folder 958)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1966 Mar-Apr (Box 81, Folder 959)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1966 May-Jun (Box 81, Folder 960)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1966 Jul-Sep (Box 81, Folder 961)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1966 Oct (Box 81, Folder 962)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1966 Nov-Dec (Box 81, Folder 963)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1967 Jan-Feb (Box 81, Folder 964)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1967 Mar-May (Box 81, Folder 965)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1967 Jul-Nov (Box 81, Folder 966)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 967)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1970-1971 (Box 81, Folder 968)
    - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1973-1975 (Box 81, Folder 969)
    - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh, 1947-1952 (Box 81, Folder 970)
    - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 971)
    - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 972)
    - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 973)
    - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh, 1956-1957 (Box 81, Folder 974)
    - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh, 1959-1961 (Box 81, Folder 975)
    - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh, 1962-1964 (Box 81, Folder 976)
    - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh, 1965-1970, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 977)
    - Rhode Island: Providence, 1965 (Box 82, Folder 978)
    - Rhode Island: Providence, 1966 Jan-Mar (Box 82, Folder 979)
    - Rhode Island: Providence, 1966 Apr-Jun (Box 82, Folder 980)
    - Rhode Island: Providence, 1966 Jul-Dec (Box 82, Folder 981)
    - Rhode Island: Providence, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 982)
    - Rhode Island: Providence, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 983)
    - Tennessee: Nashville, 1954-1960 (Box 82, Folder 984)
    - Texas: Dallas-Fort Worth, 1953-1954 (Box 82, Folder 985)
    - Texas: Dallas-Fort Worth, 1955-1956 (Box 82, Folder 986)
    - Texas: Dallas-Fort Worth, 1961 Jan (Box 82, Folder 987)
    - Texas: Dallas-Fort Worth, 1961 Apr (Box 82, Folder 988)
    - Texas: Dallas-Fort Worth, 1961 May-Aug (Box 82, Folder 989)
    - Texas: Dallas-Fort Worth, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 990)
    - Virginia: Richmond, 1953 (Box 82, Folder 991)
    - Virginia: Richmond, 1965-1966 (Box 82, Folder 992)
    - Virginia: Richmond, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 993)
    - Virginia: Richmond, 1970-1972 (Box 82, Folder 994)
    - Virginia: Richmond, 1973-1975 (Box 82, Folder 995)
    - Washington: Seattle, 1953-1957 (Box 82, Folder 996)
    - Washington: Seattle, 1964-1965 (Box 82, Folder 997)
    - Washington: Seattle, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 998)
    - Washington: Seattle, 1967-1969 (Box 82, Folder 999)
    - Washington: Seattle, 1970-1972 (Box 82, Folder 1000)
    - Wisconsin: Madison, 1959, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 1001)
    - Wisconsin: Milwaukee, 1958-1971 (Box 82, Folder 1002)
    - Canada, 1950-1952 (Box 82, Folder 1003)
    - Canada, 1953-1954 (Box 82, Folder 1004)
    - Canada, 1955-1959 (Box 82, Folder 1005)
- Publications, Series VI
  The first folder in this Series contains an index to early R.E.A. publications. The remainder of the Series is divided into three sections: Periodicals, Newsletters, and Pamphlets.
  - Index to Publications of R.E.A., 1903 Feb-1912 Feb, 1903-1912 (Box 83, Folder 1006)
  - Periodicals
    - Religious Education
      - Correspondence regarding content, 1927-1936 (Box 83, Folder 1007-1010)
      - Correspondence regarding content, 1969-1976 (Box 83, Folder 1011)
      - Correspondence with printer, 1967-1981 (Box 83, Folder 1012-1013)
      - Preparation for June 1938 issue (Box 83, Folder 1014)
      - Preparation for Jan/Feb 1964 issue, 1963-1964 (Box 83, Folder 1015)
      - Preparation for Sep/Oct 1975 issue (Box 83, Folder 1016)
      - Preparation for Nov/Dec 1980 issue, 1974-1980 (Box 84, Folder 1017)
      - Miscellaneous material re. advertising and. procedure, 1930-1974, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 1018)
      - Publicity, 1963-1977 (Box 84, Folder 1019)
      - Seminar paper re. Religious Education by Sister Mary Margaret Funk, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 1020)
      - Pre-prints, 1940-1958 (Box 84, Folder 1021)
      - Reprints, 1940-1960 (Box 84, Folder 1022-1023)
      - Periodicals Religious Education, 1962 (Box 84, Folder 1024)
      - Reprints, 1963-1972 (Box 84, Folder 1025)
    - Character
      - Volume 1, No. 1-4, 1934-1935 (Box 84, Folder 1026)
      - Volume 1/2, No. 5-6, 1935 (Box 84, Folder 1027)
      - Volume 1/2, No. 7-9, 1936 (Box 85, Folder 1028)
    - Character in Everyday Life
      - Volume 3, No. 1-4, 1936 (Box 85, Folder 1029)
      - Volume 3, No. 5-10, 1937 (Box 85, Folder 1030)
      - Volume 4, No. 1-5, 1937-1938 (Box 85, Folder 1031)
      - Volume 4, No. 6-10, 1938 (Box 85, Folder 1032)
    - Character and Citizenship
      - Volume 5, No. 1-4, 1938 (Box 85, Folder 1033)
      - Volume 5, No. 5-7, 1939 (Box 85, Folder 1034)
      - Volume 5, No. 8-10, 1939 (Box 85, Folder 1035)
      - Volume 6, No. 1-3, 1939 (Box 86, Folder 1036)
      - Volume 6, No. 4-6, 1939-1940 (Box 86, Folder 1037)
    - The American Citizen
      - Volume 6, No. 7-8, 1940 (Box 86, Folder 1038)
      - Volume 6, No. 9-10, 1940 (Box 86, Folder 1039)
      - Volume 7, No. 1-3, 1940 (Box 86, Folder 1040)
      - Volume 7, No. 4-7, 1940-1941 (Box 86, Folder 1041)
      - Volume 8, No. 1, 1941 (Box 86, Folder 1042)
    - Character and Citizenship
      - Volumes 9-10 (extra copies), 1944-1945 (Box 86, Folder 1043)
      - Volumes 9-10 (bound volume), 1944-1947 (Box 87, Folder 1044)
  - Newsletters
    - "R.E.A. Newsletter", 1938 (Box 87, Folder 1045)
    - "The Religious Educator", 1971-1974 (Box 87, Folder 1046)
    - "REACH", 1975-1988 (Box 87, Folder 1047-1050)
  - Pamphlets
    - "Creative Curriculum Building for Moral and Religious Education," by E. Chave, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 1051)
    - "Highlights of Recommendations for Research," ed. by H. Wornom, 1959 (Box 87, Folder 1052)